sandhills.com 2011-09-28

# Sandhills Publishing Privacy Policy

| 

**Sandhills Publishing® Privacy Policy**  
  
---  
  
* * *  

Sandhills Publishing understands the concerns people have about privacy and safety while using the Internet. This Privacy Policy explains what information we gather from visitors, how we use that information, and the steps we take to protect your privacy.  
---  
| 1. | Sandhills Publishing collects information from visitors through voluntary site registration, voluntary submission of information when purchasing products or completing an online employment application, and through the voluntary acceptance of cookies. Sandhills Publishing will not collect information from you if you do not want us to collect it.  
---|---  
2. | Sandhills Publishing uses cookies (small pieces of code delivered to visitors' systems) to learn more about the way in which people use our site. We do not perform any individual analysis of this data and are not interested in individual information. Cookies allow us to tell what type of browsers our audience uses, which helps us to design our site so that everyone can access it. We also find out how people are using our site (what parts of the site get viewed more than others), which helps us make better content and layout decisions.   
3. | We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [Click Here for More Information](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)  
4. | When people purchase issues or subscriptions at our site, it's important that the information they enter is secure. That's why we use SSL encryption and digital certificates to verify transactions.   
5. | Sandhills Publishing uses a secure firewall to keep out unauthorized users and ensure the integrity of our systems. We are vigilant about protecting our site from unwanted intrusions.  
6. | Sandhills Publishing does **not** sell, trade, or otherwise release any personal information on our site visitors or subscribers. We respect your desire for privacy and zealously protect any information you give us. Your information is safe with us!  
7. | We are participants in the BBBOnLine® Reliability Program. Our company has been in business since 1978, and we have always strived to provide the best customer service available.  
If you have any questions at all about our Privacy Policy or our Web site, [**please send us a message**](mailto:feedback@sandhills.com).Thank you for visiting our site.
